Guide to the North Carolina State University, Athletics, Men's Basketball Audiovisual Materials
North Carolina State University, Athletics, Men's Basketball Audiovisual Materials
1953-1994, undated
1953 1994
North Carolina State University Athletics
UA 015.402
The North Carolina State University, Athletics, Men's Basketball Audio/Visual Materials collection contains primarily moving image recordings of North Carolina State University Men's basketball games. Many of these recordings were captured by the Department of Athletics for coaching and review purposes, and are mostly without sound, commentary, or other narration. Also included in this collection are a number of broadcast recordings centering around the NCAA championship titles of 1974 and 1983; as well as miscellaneous footage of individual players and coaches at NC State. Materials range in date from 1953 to 1994, with a number of films undated.
In 1911, North Carolina College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts played its first official basketball games against Wake Forest, with A&M College's home game played in the Pullen Hall auditorium. The A&M basketball team was known as the "Red Terrors" until 1947 when all the NC State sports teams adopted the name Wolfpack. The Red Terrors played home games in Raleigh's Memorial Auditorium until Thompson Gymnasium was opened in 1925. Thompson Gymnasium (now Thompson Hall) served as the home of the Men's Basketball team until Reynolds Coliseum opened in 1949. In 1930, Morris Johnson became the first NC State basketball player to receive All-American honors. On April 26, 1946, Everett Case was hired as Men's Basketball head coach, with duties beginning on July 1, 1946. Case coached at NC State until 1965, and remains the winningest basketball coach in the school's history. In 1954 the Men's Basketball team wins the Atlantic Coast Conference championship for the inaugural year of competition in the newly-formed conference. Al Heartley became the first African-American to be awarded a basketball scholarship at NC State. He later became the first African-American captain of the team (1970-1971), and the first African-American to win the Alumni Athletics trophy (1971). On March 25, 1974, NC State won its first NCAA championship over Marquette, 76-64. In April 1983, NC State won its second NCAA tournament title led by Coach Jim Valvano. All three seniors from the Championship team were selected in the NBA draft. On November 19, 1999 the Men's Basketball team beat Georgia 67-63 in its first appearance in the RBC Center (now PNC Arena).
44.5 linear feet
North Carolina State University Libraries, Special Collections Research Center
USE COPIES OF ALL RECORDINGS MUST BE PRODUCED PRIOR TO PATRON VIEWING.
Transferred from North Carolina State University, Athletics Department.
USE COPIES OF ALL RECORDINGS MUST BE PRODUCED PRIOR TO PATRON VIEWING. Recordings are arranged chronologically by date. Some seasons have general footage (not from a specific game or opponent); these recordings can be found listed after all of the game footage from that season. Recordings that could not be identified by date have been gathered at the end of the collection.
In 1911, North Carolina College of Agriculture and Mechanic Arts played its first official basketball games against Wake Forest, with A College's home game played in the Pullen Hall auditorium. The A basketball team was known as the "Red Terrors" until 1947 when all the NC State sports teams adopted the name Wolfpack. The Red Terrors played home games in Raleigh's Memorial Auditorium until Thompson Gymnasium was opened in 1925. Thompson Gymnasium (now Thompson Hall) served as the home of the Men's Basketball team until Reynolds Coliseum opened in 1949. In 1930, Morris Johnson became the first NC State basketball player to receive All-American honors. On April 26, 1946, Everett Case was hired as Men's Basketball head coach, with duties beginning on July 1, 1946. Case coached at NC State until 1965, and remains the winningest basketball coach in the school's history. In 1954 the Men's Basketball team wins the Atlantic Coast Conference championship for the inaugural year of competition in the newly-formed conference. Al Heartley became the first African-American to be awarded a basketball scholarship at NC State. He later became the first African-American captain of the team (1970-1971), and the first African-American to win the Alumni Athletics trophy (1971). On March 25, 1974, NC State won its first NCAA championship over Marquette, 76-64. In April 1983, NC State won its second NCAA tournament title led by Coach Jim Valvano. All three seniors from the Championship team were selected in the NBA draft. On November 19, 1999 the Men's Basketball team beat Georgia 67-63 in its first appearance in the RBC Center (now PNC Arena).
The North Carolina State University, Athletics, Men's Basketball Audiovisual Materials contains primarily moving image recordings of North Carolina State University Men's basketball games. Many of these recordings were captured by the Department of Athletics for coaching and review purposes, and are mostly without sound, commentary, or other narration. Also included in this collection are a number of broadcast recordings centering around the NCAA championship titles of 1974 and 1983; as well as miscellaneous footage of individual players and coaches at NC State. Materials range in date from 1954 to 1994, and some films are undated.
North Carolina State University Athletics; North Carolina State University Athletics; North Carolina State University--Sports--History; North Carolina State University--History; North Carolina State College--History; North Carolina State College--Basketball; North Carolina College athletes; North Carolina Basketball
- NC State Basketball Highlights, 1953-1954 (Carton 1)
- NC State Basketball Highlights (1 of 3), 1954-1955 (Carton 1)
- NC State Basketball Highlights (2 of 3), 1954-1955 (Carton 1)
- NC State Basketball Highlights (3 of 3), 1954-1955 (Carton 1)
- NC State Basketball Highlights, 1955-1956, 1956-1957 (Carton 1)
- NC State Basketball Highlights, 1955-1959, 1956-1957 (Carton 1)
- NC State Basketball Highlights, 1955-1959, 1956-1957 (Carton 1)
- NC State vs. South Carolina, 1957 (Carton 1)
- NC State Mens Basketball Highlights, 1957, 1958 (Carton 1)
- NC State Mens Basketball Highlights, 1957-1958 (Carton 1)
- Ronnie Shavlik, undated (Carton 1)
  VHS
- NC State Basketball Highlights - Original, 1957-1958 (Carton 2)
- NC State Basketball Highlights - Negative, 1957-1958 (Carton 2)
- NC State Basketball Highlights - Composite Copy, 1957-1958 (Carton 2)
- NC State Basketball Highlights - Color Internegative, 1957-1958 (Carton 2)
- NC State Basketball Highlights, 1957-1958 (Carton 2)
- 1958 ACC Game: Jim Reid Calling, NCSU vs. Carolina (Tape 1) (Carton 2)
  Quarter-inch audio tape reel
- 1958 ACC Game: Jim Reid Calling, NCSU vs. Carolina (Tape 2) (Carton 2)
- 1958 ACC Game: Jim Reid Calling, NCSU vs. Carolina (Tape 3) (Carton 2)
- NC State Basketball Highlights, 1957-1958 (Carton 2)
- NC State Basketball Highlights, 1959-1960 (Carton 2)
- NC State Basketball Highlights, 1959-1960 (Carton 2)
- NC State Basketball Highlights, 1959-1960 (Carton 2)
- NC State Basketball Highlights, 1959-1960 (Carton 2)
- Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 1959-1960 (Carton 2)
- Bill Russell, Fast Break, 1960 (Carton 2)
- Duke vs. Maryland, 1959-1960 (Carton 2)
- Wake Forest vs. Duke, 1959-1960 (Carton 2)
- Wake Forest vs. Duke, 1959-1960 (Carton 2)
- Wake Forest vs. Duke, 1959-1960 (Carton 2)
- Wake Forest vs. Maryland, 1959-1960 (Carton 2)
- Wake Forest vs. Maryland, 1959-1960 (Carton 2)
- 1965 ACC Tourney State vs. Duke (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Houston University, 1967 (Carton 3)
- 1967 Hi-Lite Film (Carton 3)
- Eddie Biedenbach, 1967-1968 (Carton 3)
- ACC Tournament 1970: Coaches' Interviews (Carton 3)
  quarter-inch audio reel
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 29 February 1972 (Carton 3)
- Duplicate of NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill Men's Basketball, 29 February 1972 (Carton 3)
- Duplicate of NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill Men's Basketball, 29 February 1972 (Carton 3)
- Duplicate of NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill Men's Basketball, 29 February 1972 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 12 December 1972 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest, 15 December 1972 (Carton 3)
- State vs. Wake Forest (David Thompson jersey), 1972-1975 (Carton 3)
  16mm Film Reel
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 16 December 1972 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 16 December 1972 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. University of Virginia, 6 January 1973 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 3), 10 January 1973 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 3), 10 January 1973 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 3), 10 January 1973 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 5 February 1973 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 3), 21 February 1973 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 3), 21 February 1973 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 3), 21 February 1973 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. Clemson Slo-Mo outs, 24 February 1973 (Carton 3)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, 29 February 1972 (Carton 3)
- Tommy Burleson, 1971-1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. University of California, Los Angeles, NCAA Finals, 1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. University of California, Los Angeles #2, 15 December 1973 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs Virginia, 1973-1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Maryland "Super Sunday" (1 of 4), 13 January 1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Maryland "Super Sunday" (2 of 4), 13 January 1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. UCLA, 1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Maryland "Super Sunday" (3 of 4), 13 January 1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Maryland "Super Sunday" (4 of 4), 13 January 1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. Maryland, 30 January 1974 (Carton 4)
- David Thompson TV Tape, 21 February 1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (Slo-Mo), 26 February 1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (No. 1), 26 February 1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (No. 2), 26 February 1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 3), 26 February 1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 3), 26 February 1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 3), 26 February 1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (Slo-Mo), 03 March 1974 (Carton 4)
- NC State vs. University of California, Los Angeles 2nd O.T., 23 March 1974 (Carton 4)
- "Showdown in Raleigh" Norm Sloan Show, 1974 (Carton 4)
- 1974 Highlights (Carton 4)
- Championship Games 1974 (Carton 4)
- NCAA Finals 1974, 27 May 2005 (Carton 4)
- ACC Championship Game NC State vs Maryland (1 of 1), undated (Carton 4)
- Mrs Sloan, 10 February 1974 (Carton 5)
- Film Transfer of AV.FM: .40.MB, .41.MB, .45.MB, .25.MB, .385.MB, .388.MB, 1972 - 1974 (Carton 5)
- Film Transfer of 43.65 and last segment of 43.56, undated (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (State Offense Only), 1974-1975 (Carton 5)
- ACC 1975 Highlights color sound release print (Carton 5)
- 1975 ACC Basketball Highlights (Carton 5)
- Film Transfer of AV.FM: .54.MB, .158.MB, .192.MB, .269.MB, 1975-1979 (Carton 5)
- Control, undated (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest, [1974] (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest, [1972-1975] (Carton 3)
  16mm film reel
- Mrs Sloan #4, undated (Carton 5)
- Norm Sloan, undated (Carton 5)
- Mrs Sloan feature: A-roll and B-roll, undated (Carton 5)
- Sloan Show feature, undated (Carton 5)
- State basketball, undated (Carton 5)
- NC State/UNC-Chapel Hill: Outakes, undated (Carton 5)
- Equipment feature, undated (Carton 5)
- NC State/UNC-Chapel Hill: Outs, undated (Carton 5)
- Mrs Sloan Feature, undated (Carton 5)
- Glenn Sudhop B-Roll, undated (Carton 5)
- Mrs Sloan "B" Roll 3 Cuts, undated (Carton 5)
- Untitled, undated (Carton 5)
- Mrs Sloan feature: A-roll and B-roll #2, undated (Carton 5)
- #5 NC State/UNC-Chapel Hill, undated (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. UNC, [1972-1976] (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. Maryland, Post Game, undated (Carton 5)
- [NC State vs. Maryland 1974?], undated (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. Virginia ACC Championship, undated (Carton 5)
- NC State Film Transfers and last segment, undated (Carton 5)
- Untitled, undated (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. Georgia; Slo-mo outs, undated (Carton 5)
- Red and White Outs, undated (Carton 5)
- [NC State vs. Maryland, 1974] (Carton 5)
- N.C. State vs. UNC (UNC player Mitch Kupchak's Jersey can be seen), [1972-1976] (Carton 5)
- N.C. State Film Transfers, undated (Carton 5)
- Untitled, undated (Carton 5)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill, undated (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. University of California, Los Angeles Slo-mo outs St Louis, 1974 (Carton 6)
- Big 4 Slo-mo, 1974 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Pitt (1 of 2), 28 December 1974 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Pitt (2 of 2), 28 December 1974 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Duke Big 4 (1 of 4), 02 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Duke Big 4 (2 of 4), 02 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Duke Big 4 (3 of 4), 02 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Duke Big 4 (4 of 4), 02 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 4), 03 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 4), 03 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 4), 03 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 4), 03 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (1 of 5), 07 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (2 of 5), 07 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (3 of 5), 07 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (4 of 5), 07 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (5 of 5), 07 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 4), 14 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 4), 16mm film (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 4), 14 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 4), 14 January 1976 (Carton 6)
- NC State vs. Maryland ACC Championship, 1974 (Carton 6)
- Basketball Spots- NC State "A" roll, 15 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- Basketball Spots- NC State "B" roll, 15 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 4), 24 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 4), 24 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 4), 24 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 4), 24 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 5), 28 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 5), 28 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 5), 28 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 5), 28 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 5), 28 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 4), 31 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 4), 31 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 4), 31 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 4), 31 January 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 4), 3 February 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 4), 3 February 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 4), 3 February 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 4), 3 February 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Furman (1 of 4), 6 February 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Furman (2 of 4), 6 February 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Furman (3 of 4), 6 February 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Furman (4 of 4), 6 February 1976 (Carton 7)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (1 of 4), 07 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (2 of 4), 07 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (3 of 4), 07 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (4 of 4), 07 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. UNC-Charlotte (1 of 4), 11 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. UNC-Charlotte (2 of 4), 11 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. UNC-Charlotte (3 of 4), 11 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. UNC-Charlotte (4 of 4), 11 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. UNC-Charlotte (1 of 1), 11 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 4), 14 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 4), 14 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 4), 14 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 4), 14 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest Basketball (1 of 1), 14 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Duke (1 of 5), 18 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Duke (2 of 5), 18 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Duke (3 of 5), 18 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Duke (4 of 5), 18 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Duke (5 of 5), 18 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 4), 21 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 4), 21 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 4), 21 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 4), 21 February 1976 (Carton 8)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (1 of 4), 24 February 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 4), 24 February 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 4), 24 February 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 4), 24 February 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 4), 28 February 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 4), 28 February 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 4), 28 February 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 4), 28 February 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Holy Cross (1 of 4), 15 March 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Holy Cross (2 of 4), 15 March 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Holy Cross (3 of 4), 15 March 1996 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Holy Cross (4 of 4), 15 March 1996 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. UNC-Charlotte (1 of 2), 18 March 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. UNC-Charlotte (2 of 2), 18 March 1976 (Carton 9)
- David Thompson, 27 April 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Penn State (1 of 4), 04 December 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Penn State (2 of 4), 04 December 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Penn State (3 of 4), 04 December 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Penn State (4 of 4), 04 December 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (1 of 3), 08 December 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (2 of 3), 08 December 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Arizona State (3 of 3), 08 December 1976 (Carton 9)
- NC State vs. Reno (1 of 4), 11 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. Reno (2 of 4), 11 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. Reno (3 of 4), 11 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. Reno (4 of 4), 11 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. Michigan State (1 of 1), 20 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. Oregon State (1 of 2), 22 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. Oregon State (2 of 2), 22 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- Sloan Feature, 26 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. Rice (1 of 4), 29 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. Rice (2 of 4), 29 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. Rice (3 of 4), 29 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. Rice (4 of 4), 29 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. East Carolina (1 of 4), 30 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. East Carolina (2 of 4), 30 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. East Carolina (3 of 4), 30 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. East Carolina (4 of 4), 30 December 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. Providence (1 of 4), January 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. Providence (2 of 4), January 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. Providence (3 of 4), January 1976 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. Providence (4 of 4), January 1976 (Carton 10)
- 1976 ACC Basketball Highlights (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 4); NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 4), 24 February 1976; 18 January 1978 (Carton 10)
- NC State vs. A&T (1 of 4), 03 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. A&T (2 of 4), 03 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. A&T (3 of 4), 03 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. A&T (4 of 4), 03 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina (1 of 4), 05 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina (2 of 4), 05 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina (3 of 4), 05 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Western Carolina (4 of 4), 05 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 4), 09 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 4), 09 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 4), 09 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 4), 09 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 3), 27 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 3), 27 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 3), 27 January 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 3), 01 February 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 3), 01 February 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 3), 01 February 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (1 of 4), 05 February 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (2 of 4), 05 February 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (3 of 4), 05 February 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Georgia Tech (4 of 4), 05 February 1977 (Carton 11)
- NC State vs. Clemson (1 of 4), 19 February 1977 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Clemson (2 of 4), 19 February 1977 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Clemson (3 of 4), 19 February 1977 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Clemson (4 of 4), 19 Febraury 1977 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 4), 02 December 1977 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 4), 02 December 1977 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 4), 02 December 1977 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 4), 02 December 1977 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (Big Four) (1 of 4), 02 December 1977 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (Big Four) (2 of 4), 02 December 1977 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (Big Four) (3 of 4), 02 December 1977 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (Big Four) (4 of 4), 02 December 1977 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. St Joe (1 of 3), 28 December 1977 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. St Joe (2 of 3), 28 December 1977 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. St Joe (3 of 3), 28 December 1977 (Carton 12)
- 1977 ACC Basketball Highlights (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. UNC- Chapel Hill (1 of 4), 18 January 1978 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (2 of 4), 18 January 1978 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (3 of 4), 18 January 1978 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. UNC-Chapel Hill (4 of 4), 18 January 1978 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Furman (1 of 1), 04 February 1978 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (1 of 4), 11 February 1978 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (Reel 2 of 4), 11 Feb 1978 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (2 of 4), 11 February 1978
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (3 of 4), 11 February 1978 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Wake Forest (4 of 4), 11 February 1978 (Carton 12)
- NC State vs. Maryland ACC Tournament (1 of 6), 01 March 1978 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Maryland ACC Tournament (2 of 6), 01 March 1978 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Maryland ACC Tournament (3 of 6), 01 March 1978 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Maryland ACC Tournament (4 of 6), 01 March 1978 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Maryland ACC Tournament (5 of 6), 01 March 1978 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Maryland ACC Tournament (6 of 6), 01 March 1978 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Appalachian State, 02 January 1979 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Maryland (1 of 5), 10 January 1979 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Maryland (2 of 5), 10 January 1979 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Maryland (3 of 5), 10 January 1979 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Maryland (4 of 5), 10 January 1979 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Maryland (5 of 5) O.T., 10 January 1979 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Virginia (1 of 4), 13 January 1979 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Virginia (2 of 4), 13 January 1979 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Virginia (3 of 4), 13 January 1979 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. Virginia (4 of 4), 13 January 1979 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. UNC- Chapel Hill (1 of 5), 17 January 1979 (Carton 13)
- NC State vs. UNC- Chapel Hill (2 of 5), 17 January 1979 (Carton 13)